Wilson Fernando Andrade Córdoba Java Senior Developer

CONTACTS

- **C** + 57 (311) 7004760

de Neiva - Huila

SKILLS

- SalServer OracleDB
- Postgrest
- Mysql
- Scrum
- **GIT**
- Junit
- Spring

- Linux
- Windows

- Reactor
- CI/CD
- Wiremock

BmSoftware, Cali, Colombia | Software Developer

- -Designed generic libraries for uploading files.
- -Designed generic interface providing a server push.
- -Led the team into agile methodologies with Scrum.

REFERENCES

Jefferson Perez Cervera Systems Engineer 316 6887165

Wilson Andrade González Public Accountant 314 3829579

HOBBIES







- **C** + 57 (304) 5829398

C.C. 1075229917

- **JSE**
 - **Drools**
 - Docker
 - SpringBoot

 - Mutation Test

LANGUAGES

Spanish:

CAREER SUMMARY

Wilson Fdo. worked as software developer for more than 7 years. He works with Java technologies in agile environments using Scrum. He has great-problemsolving-skills and is constantly studying and learning about new technologies and techniques.

EDUCATION

Universidad del Valle

Systems engineer IV semesters

2007

Sena

B.Tech, Analysis and Development of Information Systems

2010

Scrum Agile Institute

Certified Scrum Developer

2016



EXPERIENCE

EPAM Anywhere, Medellin, Colombia I Java Senior Developer at Amwell

Abr. 2022 - Today

- -Back-end Java developer dedicated to the analysis, design, development.
- -Worked with AWS
- -Designed RESTful APIs for microsystem environments.
- -Worked with CI/CD with Gitlab.

Mercado Libre, Medellin, Colombia | Java Senior Developer

Dic. 2021 - Mar. 2022

- -Worked on the back-end development on a micro-services architectural base.
- -Involved in new features development and bug fixing of existing microservices applications.
- -Design and implement Integration Test.
- -Coaching and help the junior developers, promoting their growth through collaborative team design and review sessions.

Globant, Medellin, Colombia | Java Senior Developer at Disney

Feb. 2020 - Nov. 2021

- -Back-end Java developer dedicated to the analysis, design, development, implementation of Scheduling core systems.
- -Designed RESTful APIs for microsystem environments.
- -Instrumentation and observability using newrelic and micrometer.
- -Worked with CI/CD with Gitlab.
- -Implemented high responsive systems using Reactive Programing (Reactor).

Globant, Medellin, Colombia | Java Developer at ESPN

Nov. 2018 – Feb. 2020

Aug. 2017 – Oct. 2018

- -Back-end Java developer dedicated to the analysis, design, development, implementation and maintenance of AlS core applications.
- -Designed RESTful APIs.
- -Implemented business logic using Drools.